Class of 1915 Records, 1911-1985
Smith College Archives
Class of 1915 Records
1911-1985
Smith College. Class of 1915.
RG 80 UUID:e79bb5bb-fbf6-46d9-a99e-69e3c3e10bd4
18 boxes (12.5 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 18 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1915.
The Class of 1915 was the thirty-sixth entering class and the thirty-sixth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1915 records, 1911-1985, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1915, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, programs, Secretary's notes, Treasurer's notes, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1915 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- General 1914, 1982, undated (Box 1870, Folder 1)
- Baccalaureate 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 2)
- Clippings 1915-1916, 1940 (Box 1870, Folder 3)
- Collation 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 4)
- Commencement 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 5)
- Commencement Music 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 6)
- Commencement Photographs 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 7)
- Freshman Grind by 1914 1911 (Box 1870, Folder 8)
- Groups 1911-1915 (Box 1870, Folder 9)
- Hoop Rolling 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 11)
- Ivy Day Photographs 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 12)
- Junior Ushers 1914 (Box 1870, Folder 13)
- Junior Prom 1914 (Box 1870, Folder 14)
- Junior Prom-Garden Party 1914 (Box 1870, Folder 15)
- Last Chapel 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 16)
- Last Sing 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 17)
- Class Letters 1924-1985 (Box 1870, Folder 18)
- Loan Forms for Paintings from Museum of Art 1969 (Box 1870, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1916 (Box 1871, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1925-1928 (Box 1871, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1930 (Box 1871, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1935 (Box 1871, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1940 (Box 1871, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1940 (Box 1871, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1950-1955 (Box 1871, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1960-1965 (Box 1871, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1970 (Box 1871, Folder 9)
- Reunions: Correspondence 1975 (Box 1871, Folder 10)
- Reunions: Material Collected by Marian Palmer Faulkner 1975 (Box 1871, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1975 (Box 1871, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1980-1986 (Box 1871, Folder 13)
- Reunion Songs undated (Box 1871, Folder 14)
- Class of 1915 (Box 1872)
- Senior Parties 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 1)
- Smock Day 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 2)
- Sophomore Push Committee 1913 (Box 1872, Folder 3)
- Sophomore Reception 1912 (Box 1872, Folder 4)
- Songs undated (Box 1872, Folder 5)
- Step Sings 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 6)
- Senior Dramatics 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 7)
- Senior Dramatics: Business Manager's Ledger 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 8)
- Senior Dramatics: Photographs 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 9)
- Senior Dramatics: Photographs 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 10)
- Class Supper 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 11)
- Treasurer Account Ledger 1954-1978 (Box 1872, Folder 12)
- Class Secretary's Notes-A-Behrens (Box 1872, Folder 1)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Bell-Bradt (Box 1872, Folder 2)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Breckenridge-Buttler (Box 1872, Folder 3)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Carpenter-Collins (Box 1872, Folder 4)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Cooke-Damon (Box 1872, Folder 5)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Deney-Egbert (Box 1872, Folder 6)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Evans-Frey (Box 1872, Folder 7)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Friel-Gibbons (Box 1873, Folder 1)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Gibling-Griffith (Box 1873, Folder 2)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Hills-Hoyt (Box 1873, Folder 3)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Hoyt-Mather (Box 1873, Folder 4)
- Class Secretary's Notes-McCormick-Merriam (Box 1873, Folder 5)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Myers-Park (Box 1873, Folder 6)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Park-Peters (Box 1873, Folder 7)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Pomeroy-Ramsdell (Box 1873, Folder 8)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Reed-Robinson (Box 1873, Folder 9)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Rowe-Scannell (Box 1873, Folder 10)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Scriber-Sibley (Box 1873, Folder 11)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Swartwout-Smith (Box 1873, Folder 12)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Spencer-Stobie (Box 1873, Folder 13)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Storey-Thayer (Box 1873, Folder 14)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Tierney-Tuttle (Box 1873, Folder 15)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Twyeffort-Wainwright (Box 1873, Folder 16)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Walker-Washburn (Box 1873, Folder 17)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Waterman-Watters (Box 1873, Folder 18)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Whaley-Wood (Box 1873, Folder 19)
- Class Secretary's Notes-Wood-Yount (Box 1873, Folder 20)
- Class Secretary's Photo Album (Box OV)
- Reunions-Costume and Banner (Box OV)